Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♪The moon rests on the treetops,
listening to the evening breeze♪
♪Wine in hand,
I sing as stars shine in disarray♪
♪The endless night
keeps but one lonely lamp♪
♪Who knows if I'm warm or cold♪
♪Years of companionship
vanish like mist♪
♪How many roads must a deep love travel♪
♪The returned soul
wears robes of regret♪
♪Brushing off dust with a wave♪
♪Wind or no wind, I think of you♪
♪Beyond words♪
♪A vow is cherished all the time♪
♪Some souls yearn to ferment time♪
♪Into a story♪
♪Crushing the past,
I let old memories fade♪
♪Don't let this story end♪
=Beyond The Loop=
=Episode 11=
Why have I been craving
sour foods so much these days?
My period hasn't come this month.
No way!
(Congratulations.
I noticed a pregnancy pulse.)
(Please take care of your body)
(and do not exhaust yourself.)
(Shili Pavilion)
Godmother.
Starting today, I must return
to the City Lord's Mansion.
Sorry for bothering you these days.
Thank you for your care.
You're leaving?
A couple should face hardships together.
I can't leave him
to face all this alone.
Fine.
If you insist on leaving,
I won't stop you.
But I hope you could
give Qiming a proper explanation.
Of course.
However, Godmother.
There's one thing I'd like to ask you.
I was once hunted by a group of people.
And all of them had
this tattoo on their wrists.
Godmother, do you know
something about these people?
Such an ordinary pattern,
how could I possibly remember it?
You'd better ask someone else.
But this paper
was found in the pastry box
from the Shili Pavilion.
Godmother, please tell me the truth.
This is crucial to me.
Some things
will only bring you trouble if you know.
It'd better not knowing.
But they tried to kill me several times.
I just don't
want to die without knowing why.
Don't you even
grant me this small wish?
I'm a businesswoman. I work for money.
As for those pastries you mentioned,
they were all delivered by others.
Why would I pay attention to some paper?
Wan, all I can promise you
is that when you're in danger,
I will certainly save you.
But I can't tell you anything more.
Thank you, Godmother.
You're such a clever girl,
yet with poor taste
in choosing men.
Godmother.
Probably fate
determines it.
He's the one for me.
Miss Yu.
Are you returning
to the City Lord's Mansion?
Thank you for your care these days.
This is my gift for you.
Aren't you going to open it?
I like anything from you.
Actually, I know this day would come.
Though I'm upset,
seeing you happy
is enough for me.
Song Qiming.
No matter what happens,
we'll always be good friends.
If we actually became a couple,
we might not be able
to confide in each other
like we do now, right?
If City Lord heard this,
he'd be jealous for a year.
Alright, I'm off.
Check the gift.
(Miss Yu, may you be happy.)
Mu Yunqing.
Why is no one here to welcome me?
Yunqing!
Wan!
(Welcome home, Madam)
This is so extravagant!
Welcome home, dear.
Thank you, dear.
Do you miss me?
Yes.
My lady.
Madam.
What's this?
May you have a baby soon.
Why are you two be like Grandfather?
Grandfather.
Wan.
I have a gift for you too.
Grandfather.
This is my half a lifetime's
savings.
You must keep it well.
Don't let him steal it.
Thank you, Grandfather.
Grandfather treats me so well.
You are playing favorites.
You didn't know?
Madam, I miss you so much.
I've already cleaned your room.
You're always considerate.
I'm even more.
I've prepared you
a grand homecoming feast.
Know how to cook?
Let's go.
Forgot me already?
Grandfather.
How could we ever forget you?
- Let's go.
Let's go.
The weather is lovely today.
With such a gentle breeze.
Yunqing.
I wish we could be like this every day,
carefree and simple.
Wan.
If one day I'm no longer with you,
you must stay happy.
Never feel sad,
or shed tears.
What did you say?
Don't say things like that.
Because I love seeing you smile.
I want you to stay happy.
Then I'll smile.
- Okay.
- I'll keep smiling.
Okay. Keep smiling.
Don't say things like that.
♪You're the distant star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Spend all my devotion♪
♪For your tears and embrace♪
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪To walk with you♪
Madam, I'll be back soon.
Okay.
City Lord, we've confirmed
the residence
of the Yunluo Incense seller.
It's in the west of the city.
Inform the team. Prepare to take action.
Yes.
(Shili Pavilion)
Mother.
I didn't mean it.
Fine.
I know it's because of Miss Yu.
Her departure took your heart with her.
Mother.
I do miss her.
I understand.
I also often miss your father.
Mother, your knees are hurting again?
Just old pains. Nothing serious.
Mother.
Silly child, it doesn't kill me.
I've decided
I'll avenge you
and make those Mobei people pay.
Qiming, what did you say?
Mother.
Before, I never
understood love,
or separation.
But now I know it all.
If not for those Mobei people,
you and father wouldn't
have been separated,
and our family would still be whole.
So, I must take revenge.
Qiming, you've grown mature.
Come on, get up.
Here.
I made your favorite pastries.
Do they taste good?
Madam, what's the occasion today?
You prepared so much.
Take a guess.
If you're right, I'll tell you.
Don't tease me.
(Luoyou Villa)
♪Winter snow waltzes
before the courtyard♪
♪Palaces show no mercy♪
♪So much courage it takes♪
♪To retrace each step♪
♪Memory's whispers, dreams or illusion♪
♪Butterflies climb mountains for love♪
♪Perish before the flowers♪
♪You seem so distant,
yet right before my eyes♪
♪A game of chess, a fate of strife♪
♪I dream of standing
with you, side by side♪
♪If you would meet me face to face♪
♪I'd die without a single regret♪
♪You're the untouchable star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Through all the tides of love and hate♪
♪Our eyes met across the mortal world♪
♪When breezes stirred by my window♪
♪Cherry blossoms rained in the sky♪
♪You're the distant star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Spend all my devotion♪
♪For your tears and embrace♪
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪To walk with you♪